-嗨 -嘿
-Hi! -Hey!
有多少人会来参加 宝宝的欢迎会？
So,what's the final head count on my baby shower?
大约有20个人 有些同事有事没办法来
About twenty. Couple people from work had something else to do.
你的妹妹们打电话来说她们没办法来
Your sisters called and can't make it.
什么？ 你说她们不来参加…
What? You mean they're not coming to a social event..
没有男人跟酒的社交聚会？ 那真的是太稀奇了
where there's no men and no booze? That's shocking.
我不在乎，只要我妈能来就行了
I don't care,as long as my mom's here.
-天啊，你妈 -什么？我妈不会来吗？
-Oh,my God. Your mother. -What? My mom's not gonna be here?
说不定我们忘了邀请她 反而能让她松口气
Well,given that we forgot to invite her,it would be a big coincidence if she was.
我的天啊
My God!
不是我的错 菲比负责发请帖的
Phoebe was in charge of the invitations.
我没有妈妈 所以我常忘了…
I don't have a mother. So often I forget..
得了吧
Oh,give it a rest.
我妈妈不来参加 宝宝的欢迎会？
So my mother is not coming to my baby shower?
对
No.
我妈也不会来
Neither is mine.
我们会处理的，我们会打电话给她 你先回家做准备
We'll take care of it. We'll call her. You go home and get ready.
确定她一定会来 这很重要，她是我妈
Make sure she comes. It's important. It's my mom.
-我知道，她电话号码几号？ -我不知道
-I know. What's her number? -I don't know.
你去吧，我记在我的电话簿里了
Go. I have it in my book. Go.
如果你负责寄请帖 为什么是我打电话给她？
If you're in charge of invitations,why am I calling her?
喂，格林太太 嗨，我是莫妮卡盖勒
Hello,Mrs. Green! Hi,it's Monica Geller.
-你好，莫妮卡 -嗨
-Oh,hello,Monica. -Hi.
这是紧急通知 我们打算在今天…
It's last-minute,but we've decided to throw an impromptu..
-帮瑞秋的宝宝办欢迎会 -我的女儿们已经告诉我了…
-baby shower for Rachel today. -My daughters told me..
她们在一个月前 就接到欢迎会的请帖
when they received their impromptu invitations a month ago.
-好吧，我很抱歉 -为什么呢？亲爱的
-Okay,I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. -For what,dear?
为了没有邀请我 还是你说谎骗我呢？
For not inviting me,or for lying about it?
天啊，我的屁股在流汗
Oh,my God! My ass is sweating.
我为所有的事道歉 真的，我是说…
I'm sorry for everything. Really,I mean..
计划宝宝的欢迎会 真的累人
there's a lot of planning in a baby shower.
我们会忘了一些事 还有…
You know,things get overlooked and..
菲比的妈妈自杀了
Phoebe's mother killed herself.
为什么？ 你们也忘了邀请她？
Why? Did you forget to invite her too?
你真是幽默
Oh,you're so funny.
拜托，你能来吗？ 欢迎会四点开始
Please,please,can you come? It starts at 4:00.
-好吧，四点见 -谢谢
-Well,all right. I'll see you at 4. -Thank you.
-不是三点开始吗？ -婊子养的
-Isn't it at 3? -Son of a bitch!
本集播出：宝宝欢迎会
The.One.With.The.Baby.Shower
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
主演：寇妮考克斯
主演：丽莎库卓
主演：麦特勒布兰
主演：马修派瑞
主演：大卫修蒙
乔伊，你要去打篮球吗？
Hey,Joe! Wanna shoot some hoops?
我得告诉你 这次我不要防守那个高个子
And for the record,I am not covering the tall one this time.
好吧，但她没有那么高
Fine,but she's not that tall.
我不能去，我在练习 我要参加新游戏节目主持人的试镜
I can't go. I'm practicing. I got an audition to be the host of a new game show.
-酷啊 -太棒了
-Cool! -Great!
如果我能当上主持人 白天我是德瑞克拉莫瑞医生
If I get it,by day I'll be Dr. Drake Ramoray.
但晚上我是乔伊崔比亚尼
But by night I'll be Joey Tribbiani!
你非常适合这份工作 节目名称跟你的名字一样
You'll be perfect for this! That's already your name!
我知道
I know. I know.
我能够得到这份工作是最好的 因为谁都不知道演肥皂剧结果会怎么样
It'd be great if I got this because you never know what could happen on a soap.
但我可以一辈子 当游戏节目主持人
But I could be a game-show host forever.
就像巴伯贝克 他主持猜价游戏75年
Like that Bob Barker guy. He's been doing The Price is Right for 75 years.
我敢说前25年的收视率 一定不太好
I bet the ratings weren't good for the first 25.
那时根本没有电视机
You know,before there was television.
问题是 这项游戏真的很复杂
But the problem,this game is really complicated.
拜托 你也那么说饥饿河马
Come on. You said the same thing about Hungry Hungry Hippos.
上星期你赢了班
And last week,you beat Ben.
对 我得跟你们承认
Yeah. I have to be honest with you guys.
他故意让我赢的
He kind of let me win.
再过几小时就要试镜 我搞不懂这个游戏
The audition's in a couple hours,and I don't understand the game.
你需要帮忙吗？
Do you want some help?
真的吗？那真的太棒了 你们可以当参赛者
Oh,really? That'd be great. Hey,you guys can be the contestants!
我们可以下次 再去打败初中女生
We can lose to junior-high girls some other time.
好吧，我们来玩晕头转向
All right. Let's play Bamboozled!
-晕头转向？ -对，那个名字很酷吧？
-Bamboozled? -Yeah. Isn't that a cool name?
-对 -不
-Yeah! -No!
好吧 第一位参赛者是罗斯盖勒
All right. Okay. Our first contestant is Ross Geller.
做个自我介绍吧，罗斯
Tell us about yourself,Ross.
我是古生物学家 我住在纽约
Well,I'm a paleontologist. I live in New York.
我有个儿子叫做班，嗨，班，还有…
I have a son,Ben. Hi,Ben! And..
我叫你介绍一下自己，罗斯 你呢？钱德
I said,a little bit,Ross. How about you,Chandler?
我是个猎头 引诱那些第三世界的苏维埃科学家…
I'm a headhunter. I hook up out-of-work Soviet scientists..
辞去他们的工作 嗨，拉斯普廷
with rogue Third World nations. Hi,Rasputin.
太棒了，我们开始吧 钱德，你先
Excellent! Let's play! Chandler,you'll go first.
-哥伦比亚的首都在哪里？ -波哥大
-What is the capital of Colombia? -Bogota.
是波格大，但很接近了
It's Bogota,but close enough.
可以把机会让给罗斯 或挑魔法机会牌
You can either pass your turn to Ross or pick a Wicked Wango Card.
-魔法机会牌可以做什么？ -我早该知道的
-What does a Wicked Wango Card do? -I should know that.
让我看看，请等一下…
Let's see. One moment,please..
好了，魔法机会牌 能决定你要向上或是向下
Here we are. A Wicked Wango Card determines if you go higher or lower.
什么东西向上或是向下？
Higher or lower than what?
-这真的是太丢脸了 -你能相信这有多烂吗？
-This is embarrassing! -Can you believe how lame this is?
抱歉 我想参赛者不该交谈
I'm sorry. I don't believe contestants are allowed to talk to each other.
我叫脱衣舞男五点要到 那很棒吧？
I told the stripper to be here at 5. That's good,right?
你请脱衣舞男来宝宝欢迎会？ 那太不适当了
You ordered a stripper for the shower? That is inappropriate.
为什么？他会打扮成宝宝的样子
Why? He's gonna be dressed as a baby.
嗨，格林太太 我很高兴你赶来了
Oh,hi,Mrs. Green. I'm so glad you could make it.
谢谢你，我们很抱歉 我们真的很过意不去
Thank you so much. We're so sorry. We could not feel worse about it.
试试看吧
Try.
我女儿在那边
There's my little girl!
-她还在生气 -对，我知道
-She's still mad. -Yeah,I know.
那不是很棒吗？ 少了一个人跟你说悄悄话
Isn't it great? One less person to make small talk with.
你好吗？
Hey,how are you?
对，好吧
Yeah,yeah. Okay,okay.
菲比，珊卓拉也在生你的气 你不会感到困扰吗？
Phoebe,Sandra's mad at you too. It doesn't bother you?
我们道了两次歉 我真的没办法了
We've apologized twice. I can't do any more than that.
你讨厌 别人生你的气…
You hate it when people are mad at you..
但你得去 接受它
but you just have to be okay with it.
好吧，我办得到
Okay. I can do that.
-我得去帮我的屁股扑痱子粉 -喔
-I gotta go powder my ass. -Oh.
看看你的脸 你跟念高中时还是一样
Look at that face! Just like when you were in high school.
要不是我很了解你 我会以为你是个有麻烦的啦啦队长
If I didn't know better,I'd say you were a cheerleader in trouble.
-来吧，我们去喝点茶 -好吧
-Come,let's get some tea. -Okay.
天啊，你看 只剩三星期了
Oh,my! Look at that. Only three weeks to go.
你挑好奶妈了吗？ 如果请管家兼职，她会分心的
Did you pick a nanny? If you use your housekeeper,it will split her focus.
事实上我不请奶妈 我也没有管家
Actually,I'm not gonna use a nanny. And I don't have a housekeeper.
你好像山顶洞人
It's like you're a cave person.
你得请个奶妈 你不知道带孩子有多累
You must get a nanny. You don't know how overwhelming it will be.
你小时候我雇用了K太太
When you were a baby,I had Mrs. K.
K太太，对，她人真的很好 她教我西班牙文
Mrs. K! Oh,yeah,she was sweet. She taught me Spanish.
我想 我还记得一点
I actually think I remember some of it.
你母亲是疯了（西班牙文）
Tu madre esta loca.
她真是个好人
Such a sweet woman.
更重要的是 她成为我们家的一部份
And more important,she became a part of our family.
没错，K太太 她到底姓什么？
That's right,Mrs. K. What did that K stand for?
我不知道，亲爱的 她只是个奶妈
I have no idea,dear. She was the nanny.
她真的很棒 我出不起那笔钱
As great as she was,I can't afford that.
抱歉 有时我忘了不是大家都有赡养费
I'm sorry. Sometimes I forget not everyone has alimony.
-瑞秋 -什么？
-Oh,Rachel! -What?
我想到一个好点子 我要搬过去跟你们住
I just had a great idea! I'm gonna come live with you!
什么？
What? What?
我很高兴 我能帮我女儿这个忙
Oh,I'm so happy I'm gonna do this for my little girl.
看看你 你感动的都快哭了
Look at you. You have tears in your eyes.
没错，我是快哭了
Yes,yes,I do.
罗斯，现在是你领先
Ross,you're in the lead.
你要再回答一题 或旋转处罚轮？
Would you like to take another question or spin the Wheel of Mayhem?
今天我转轮子的运气不太好 乔伊
The Wheel has not been my friend tonight,Joey.
我要再回答一题
I'll take another question.
好吧，这题很难 仔细听好了
Okay. This is gonna be tough. Hold your breath.
没关系，我准备好了
It's okay. I'm ready.
你得注意听 再回答问题
You gotta hold your breath until you answer.
这太可笑了，他没办法注意…
This is ridiculous! He's not gonna hold his..
好吧，如果你害怕恐惧的感觉 那该怎么说？惧…
Okay. What do you have a fear of if you suffer from this phobia? Triska..
天啊，那个字真长，惧…
Holy cow. That's a big word. Trisk..
看看这个，它该怎么念？
Look at this. How do you say that?
-让我看看 -就是这个字
-Let me see that. -This one right here.
-数字十三恐惧症 -对三层夹心饼干的恐惧
-Triskaidekaphobia. -Fear of Triscuits!
-不，是对数字十三的恐惧 -对三层夹心饼干的恐惧？
-No! No. Fear of the number 13. -Fear of Triscuits?
这有可能 饼干的边缘很锋利
It's possible. They have really sharp edges.
钱德，轮到你了
Chandler,you're up.
我要用天使通行证 换免费的机会
I'm entitled to use my Angel Pass for a free turn.
对，但你只能使用一次 请考虑清楚
Yes,yes. But you can only use it once,so choose wisely.
这真的很难决定
This is tricky.
现在是我领先 但我想再试一次金猴
I mean,I am in the lead,but I would love another shot at the Golden Monkey.
-这个游戏真的很没有道理 -你很生气是因为你输了
-This game makes no sense! -You're upset because you're losing.
拜托，罗斯 我想我们都是失败者
Oh,come on,Ross. I think we're all losers here.
我想用 我的天使通行证
I would like to hang on to my Angel Pass please.
你可以选轮子 或选张谷歌搜索牌
You can either spin the Wheel or pick a Google Card.
让我想想 我不在乎
Let me think,let me think. Oh,I don't care.
你非选不可
You must choose.
-那还是没有差别 -快选吧，混蛋
-Either. It makes no difference. -Choose,you jackass.
-我要抽卡片 -你选到了给我卡
-I'll take a card. -You picked the Gimme Card!
-你拿到罗斯所有的分数 -什么？
-You get all of Ross' points! -What?
这个游戏开始好玩起来了
This game is kind of fun!
你不觉得你拿到我的分数 太疯狂了…
You don't think it's crazy that you get my points..?
参赛者 不该交谈的
The contestants aren't supposed to speak to each other.
你要开始 拆礼物了吗？
Now,do you wanna start opening presents..
因为大家 似乎急着想离开
because it seems like people are getting itchy to leave.
我说大家 指的是我自己
And when I say people,I mean me.
-你为什么要邀请我妈来？ -什么？
-Why did you invite my mother? -What?
她要搬过来跟我和罗斯住 以便帮忙照顾宝宝
She wants to move in with me and Ross to help take care of the baby.
-多久？ -八星期
-For how long? -Eight weeks.
我爱我妈，但是天啊 跟她一起吃午餐太久就是种折磨
I love my mother,but,my God,a long lunch with her is taxing.
如果她想跟我住 我会觉得很光荣
I'd be honored if she wanted to live with me.
她听不到
She can't hear you.
我该怎么样？
What am I gonna do?
如果不希望她搬过去 你该直说的
If you don't want her to move in with you,just tell her.
你说的对 我就快生了
You're right. I'm about to have a baby.
我可以说我不希望 她睡在沙发上
I can say I don't want her sleeping on my couch.
她会睡在我床上 绝不能让那种事发生
She'll wanna sleep in my bed. This can't happen.
没错
That is right.
告诉她 你不希望她搬过去跟你们住
Tell her you don't want her to live with you.
别让她拒绝你
Do not take no for an answer.
这真的太棒了 现在她会生瑞秋的气
This is great! Now she's gonna be mad at Rachel!
我要跑过去 扮她的乖女儿讨好她
And I'm just gonna swoop in there and be like the daughter she never had.
亲爱的 你得忘了这件事
Oh,honey,you have to let it go.
好吧
Okay.
谁不会接受道歉呢？
Who doesn't accept an apology?
那真的很简单
I mean,it's just so simple.
“对不起，珊卓拉” “没关系，莫妮卡”
"I'm sorry,Sandra." "That's okay,Monica.
我原谅你
I forgive you.
还有，你非常漂亮
And by the way,you're very pretty."
我真的要很尊敬钱德了
I have new respect for Chandler.
好了，大伙们 该来拆礼物了
All right,everybody! It's time to open the presents!
对 瑞秋要拆的第一样礼物…
Yes! The first gift that Rachel opens..
应该是外婆送的礼物
should be from the grandmother.
因为你是这里最重要的人 也是全世界最重要的
Because you're the most important person in this room! And in the world!
我没有准备礼物 因为我在最后一分钟才被邀请
I don't have a gift because I wasn't invited until the last minute.
但非常谢谢你，亲爱的 让大家都注意到这一点
But thank you so much,dear,for bringing that to everybody's attention.
你们这些不重要的人呢？ 我们来拆你们的礼物吧
How about you less important people? Let's open your presents!
-你没准备礼物也没关系 -但我也算是送了你一样礼物
-It's okay that you didn't get a gift. -I kind of did.
我要跟你同住八个星期
Me! Eight weeks of me.
好吧，妈妈 事实上我可以自己照顾宝宝
Okay. See,Mom,the truth is,I can do this on my own.
我知道你会是个好妈妈
I know you're gonna be a terrific mom.
但一开始你需要帮忙
But you need help at the beginning.
我知道我在做什么 我应付得来
I know what I'm doing. I can handle it.
真的吗？还记得闪光吗？
Really? Remember Twinkles?
它是只仓鼠 我不会拿吸尘器吸我的宝宝
He was a hamster. I'm not gonna vacuum up my baby!
快来吧，瑞秋 拆礼物的时间到了
Okay,come on,Rach. It's present time!
你是 这个派对的主角
You're the glue holding this party together.
现在这个派对也快毁了
It's kind of falling apart here.
-你看 -哇
-Oh,look! -Wow!
这是你同事送的
This is from your friends at work.
天啊，哇 我知道这是什么
Oh,my gosh! Oh,wow! Oh,I know what this is.
等一下
Wait a minute.
不可能
That can't be right.
这是宝宝的啤酒机吗？
Is that a beer bong for a baby?
女儿，那是挤奶器
Darling,that's a breast pump.
我说过我不再猜了吗？ 好吧，谢谢
Did I say I was done guessing? Okay,thank you for that.
哇，这是什么？
Oh,wow! What's this?
-它是尿布精灵 -它是用来放干净尿布的
-It's a Diaper Genie. -It dispenses clean diapers!
那是放脏尿布的
It's where you put dirty ones.
我为什么不直接 把尿布丢在外面的垃圾桶？
Why don't you take it outside and throw it in a dumpster?
-你每天要丢十次吗？ -什么？宝宝一天可以拉十次？
-You're gonna do that 10 times a day? -What,it goes 10 times a day?
我们得喂她印度食物吗？
Are we feeding this baby Indian food?
不，宝宝都是那样的
No,dear. That's what babies do.
瑞秋，听你妈妈的话 她非常聪明
Rachel,listen to your mother. She is very smart.
你去倒垃圾桶时 宝宝要放在哪里？
What will you do with the baby while you trot out to the garbage?
我不知道 把她放在尿布台上？
I don't know,I'd leave it on the changing table?
-什么？我做了什么？ -你不能丢下宝宝一个人
-What? What did I do? What did I do? -You can't leave a baby alone.
我当然知道
Of course,I know that!
千万不能 丢下宝宝一个人
Of course you never leave a baby alone.
它会… 她会不安全
It would.. She wouldn't be safe.
她跟我这个菜鸟妈妈在一起 也不会安全
Not as safe as she would be with me,the baby dummy.
现在拆礼物 太刺激了
Opening the presents is a little overwhelming right now.
我待会 会把它们都拆开
I'm gonna maybe open them all a little bit later.
谢谢你们赶来 还送了礼物…
Thank you for coming,for the gifts..
-这个篮子很漂亮 -它是摇篮
-and this basket is beautiful. -It's actually a bassinet.
好吧，妈妈，别离开我
Okay,Mommy,don't ever leave me.
你会在哪部电影听到这句台词？ “我们不需要臭警徽”
In what film would you hear this line: "We don't need no stinking badges!"
-《浴血金沙》 -答对了，倒念还能加分
-Treasure of the Sierra Madre! -Correct! Backwards Bonus.
-沙金血浴 -对
-Madre Sierra the of Treasure! -Yes!
什么？那样子可以加分？
What? There's extra points for that?
平公不
Fair not that's!
我要爬上机会梯 到金泥屋去
I'd like to go up the Ladder of Chance to the Golden Mud Hut!
-聪明的选择，几阶？ -六阶
-Wise choice. How many rungs? -Six!
-那个声音只代表一个意思 -饥饿的猴子
-That noise can only mean one thing. -Hungry Monkey!
-我要魔法机会牌 -这是声音题
-I'd like a Wicked Wango Card. -It's an audio question.
说出这出电视剧的主题曲
Name this television theme song:
天啊，我知道 让我想一想
Oh,my God. I know this. Give me a second.
-去跟时间乌龟说吧 -闭嘴
-Tell it to the Time Turtle! -Shut up!
-《太空仙女恋》 -答对了，你再度领先
-"I Dream of Jeannie"! -Yes! Back in the lead!
我要转轮子
I'd like to spin the Wheel.
快点
Oh,come on!
超级快速回合
Super Speedy Speed Round.
-跳跃有加分吗？ -当然
-Is there a Hopping Bonus? -Of course.
-谁发明了双焦点透镜？ -班・富兰克林
-Who invented bifocals? -Ben Franklin!
答对了 哪个君王统治英国最久？
Correct. Which monarch ruled Great Britain the longest?
维多莉亚女王
Queen Victoria!
你忘了换题时要换腿跳 跳跃动作没加分
You forgot to switch legs between questions. No Hopping Bonus!
每次都这样
Every time!
-对，现在轮到钱德了 -我要谷歌搜索卡
-Yeah. Now over to Chandler. -I'd like a Google Card.
-你确定？ -对，不，谷歌搜索卡
-Are you sure? -Yes! No! Google!
天啊，恭喜你，罗斯 因为钱德…
Oh,my God! Congratulations,Ross! Because,Chandler..
-你已经出局了 -不
-you've been Bamboozled! -No!
-对 -这是我玩过最棒的游戏
-Yes! -This is the best game ever!
只要我有需要，你就会留下来？
You'll stay as long as I need you?
-当然 -我发誓我不是白痴
-Of course. -I swear I'm not an idiot.
我看了 怀孕跟生产的书
I read books on pregnancy and giving birth.
我没有看 带孩子的书
I didn't think to read about what to do when the baby comes.
宝宝出生后…
And the baby's coming..
我不知道我该怎么办 我可以吐在尿布精灵里吗？
and I don't know what to do. Oh,can I throw up in my Diaper Genie?
亲爱的，你会没事的
Sweetie,you're gonna be fine.
-你要去哪里？ -我得上洗手间
-Where you going? -I'm going to the bathroom.
别担心 一切都会没事的
Now,don't worry. Everything's gonna be okay.
会没事的
It is gonna be okay!
这值得一试
Worth a shot.
你干嘛满脸通红全身是汗？
Hey! Why are you all red and sweaty?
我刚刚干掉了钱德
I just Bamboozled Chandler!
跟性无关
Which is not a sexual thing.
-欢迎会这么快就结束了 -因为你没来
-Well,that was a quick shower. -Not if you were here.
看来我们收到不少好礼物
Looks like we got a lot of good stuff.
没错 我妈送给我们最棒的礼物
We did. My mom got us the greatest gift of all.
培乐多理发师工具组？
A Play-Doh Barbershop?
不，她要搬过来 跟我们住八星期
No. She's going to live with us for eight weeks.
什么？
What?
对 她要帮我们照顾宝宝
Yes! She's gonna help us take care of the baby!
你不是认真的
You're not serious!
她是个好人 但我们无法忍受她八个星期
She's a very nice woman,but we can't take eight weeks of her.
-她会把我们逼疯… -嗨，罗斯
-She'll drive us crazy.. -Hi,Ross!
嘿，室友
Hey,roomie!
乔伊，我是雷 本节目的制作人
Hey,I'm Ray. I'm the producer of the show.
很荣幸能见到你，雷
It's a pleasure to meet you,Ray.
他们是唐肯跟艾玲 他们会帮你试镜
This is Duncan and Erin. They're gonna help with the audition.
-对，雷 -你准备好了就开始
-Right,Ray. -Whenever you're ready.
你好，我是乔伊崔比亚尼 我们来玩晕头转向吧
Hello. I'm Joey Tribbiani. Let's play Bamboozled!
艾玲，第一个问题，在曲棍球史上 谁被称为是“伟人”？
Erin,first question. In hockey,who is known as "The Great One"?
-葛瑞斯基 -答对了
-Gretzky. -Correct!
你要挑魔法机会卡 或转轮子？
Want to pick a Wicked Wango Card or spin the Wheel?
你的经纪人没有给你 改变过的游戏规则吗？
Didn't your agents give you the revised rules?
我们把那些东西都删掉了 没有轮子或机会卡
We've eliminated all that. No wheel. No cards.
为什么？
Why?
那太复杂了 观众没办法了解
It was too complicated. People didn't follow it.
复杂？ 转轮子上机会梯…
Complicated?! Spin the Wheel to go up the Ladder of Chance..
穿越彩虹环 找金猴
through the Rainbow Ring to the Golden Monkey.
拉它的尾巴 就能到天堂池
You yank his tail,and you're in Paradise Pond!
对，那些都删掉了
Yeah. All that's gone.
现在这只是个 简单的问答游戏
It's a simple question-and-answer game now.
那有什么好玩的呢？
Well,what's fun about that?
你要我主持 观众回答问题的无聊游戏？
You expect me to host a boring game of people answering questions?
会有比基尼女郎拿得分板
Women in bikinis hold up the scores.
我们来玩晕头转向吧
Let's play Bamboozled!
我想我们该把尿布台 放在客厅里
So I thought we'd put the changing station in the living room.
我想请我的设计师过来 因为我觉得我最擅长…
I thought I'd bring in my decorator because I feel like I'm at my best..
把房子弄得到处都是珠宝
when surrounded by jewel tones.
当然，谁不是呢？
Sure,who doesn't?
你买的那些 恐龙小玩意…
Oh,and all those dinosaur knickknacks you have..
它们或许比较适合 放在车库里
they might be more at home in the garage.
-我们没有车库 -我说车库吗？我是说垃圾桶
-Well,we don't have a garage. -Did I say garage? I meant garbage.
你知道吗？ 或许你不一定要跟我们住在一起
You know what? Maybe it's not absolutely vital that you live with us.
-瑞秋需要人帮忙带孩子 -真的，我什么都不会
-Well,Rachel needs help with the baby. -I really do. I don't know anything.
我相信那不是真的
I'm sure that's not true.
是吗？ 我会带孩子吗？
Oh,no? Do I know anything about babies?
-不 -那真的很可怕
-No. Not a thing. -It's frightening.
就算她不会 但是我会
Even if she doesn't know anything,I do.
我会教她
And I'll be there to show her.
瑞秋的爸爸 也是那么告诉我
That's exactly what Rachel's father told me.
你知道第一次半夜三点起来喂奶 他说什么吗？
Know what he said at the first 3 a.m. feeding?
“我累了，交给你吧”
"I'm tired. You take care of it."
后来他想跟我做爱时 我也是那么告诉他
Which I later said to him when he wanted to have sex.
我不是瑞秋的爸爸
Well,I'm not Rachel's dad.
我没有恶意 但他是个混蛋
And no offense,but he's an ass.
我真喜欢你，罗斯
I do like you,Ross.
我有个儿子 他妈妈跟我没有住在一起
I have a son. His mother and I didn't live together.
他跟我一起住时 我都是自己照顾他
When he was with me,I took care of him all the time,by myself.
-没错，你还有一个孩子 -对
-That's true. You do have another child. -Yeah.
跟另一个女人生的
With another woman.
你没有自制力吗？罗斯
Have you no control,Ross?
那是另一个问题
That's a different issue.
重点是宝宝出生后 我会帮忙喂她…
The point is,when the baby comes,I will be there to feed her..
帮她洗澡换尿布
and bathe her and change her.
我愿意照顾她
I want to do all those things.
-你们不需要我搬过去 -对
-You don't need me to live with you. -Yes!
对，我会想念你的
Yes. You're gonna be so missed.
-你会是个好爸爸 -你会是个好外婆
-You'll be a great father. -You'll be a wonderful grandma.
你好 我还是不知道我该做什么
Hello? I still don't know what the hell I'm doing!
新手妈妈 都会有那种感觉
Every first-time mother feels that way.
你可以慢慢学，你会的 当你刚到纽约来时…
You're gonna pick it up. Hey,you will. Look,when you first came to the city..
你是个被宠坏的无助小女孩 只会用爸爸的信用卡
you were a spoiled,helpless little girl who used Daddy's credit cards!
我希望 你真的有话要告诉我
I hope you're going somewhere with this.
看看你 你现在是个大主管
Look at you. You're this big executive.
你很能干 证明了自己的能力
You are more capable than you give yourself credit for.
我相信 你会是个好妈妈
I have no doubt you're gonna be an incredible mother.
-真的吗？ -没错
-Really? -I'm telling you.
谢谢
Thank you.
好吧，我得走了
All right. I'm gonna get going.
不，亲爱的，别送了
No,sweetheart,stay put.
我自己出去，就当我没来过这里 我差点真的来不了
I'll let myself out. It's like I'm not here. Which I almost wasn't.
你真的太幽默了 我做了什么？
You're just so funny. You're so funny. What do I do?
没什么 你跟她道歉很多次
Nothing. You have apologized to her,like,a million times.
她只是 无视你的道歉
And she's been nothing but terrible to you.
你让她女儿办了 一个可爱无聊的欢迎会
You just threw her daughter a lovely,albeit slightly boring,shower.
-她甚至没有谢谢你 -你知道吗？你说的对
-And she hasn't even thanked you for it. -You know what? You're right.
如果你有话要说 快告诉她
If you wanna say anything,I'd tell her off.
真的吗？
Really?
好吧，我会的
Okay,I will.
格林太太
Mrs. Green?
不跟主人道别 就离开派对是很无礼的
It is rude to leave a party without saying goodbye to the host.
如果有人跟你道歉 你得接受
When someone apologizes to you,the decent thing to do is to accept it.
我不是故意要那么做的
What I did wasn't on purpose.
但你对我的态度 太可耻了
But what you're doing to me now is plain spiteful.
-可耻？ -没错
-Spiteful? -That's right.
你该好好去照镜子 小姑娘
It's time you took a good look in the mirror,young lady!
老太婆
Old lady!
女士
Lady!
别说了
Wrap it up. Wrap it up. Wrap it up.
只要你准备好跟我道歉 我会原谅你
So whenever you're ready to apologize to me,I will forgive you.
再见
Good day.
我的腿没有知觉了
I can't feel my legs!
你真的太棒了 我非常以你为荣
You were fantastic! I'm so proud of you.
-是吗？我也以自己为荣 -你应该的
-Yeah? I'm proud of me too. -You should be.
-你能帮我拿杯饮料吗？ -没问题
-Could you get me something to drink? -You got it!
格林太太，我真的很抱歉 对不起，如果你…
Mrs. Green? Okay,I'm really sorry! I apologize. If you..
好吧，我咬到舌头了
Okay! I bit my tongue!
但我真的很抱歉
But I'm still really sorry!
-好吧，我准备好了 -你确定？
-Okay,I'm ready. -You sure?
我看过书 把一切都弄清楚了
I've done my studying,and I know my stuff.
好吧
All right,then.
瑞秋格林 我们来玩晕头转向
Rachel Green,let's play Bamboozled!
你该如何测试 宝宝洗澡水的温度？
How do you test the temperature of the baby's bath water?
-用手肘去试 -非常好
-Put your elbow in it. -Excellent!
-如何让宝宝小睡一下？ -喂饱她，换干尿布，趴睡，被子盖紧
-How do you put a baby down for a nap? -Full,dry,on its back,no loose covers.
答对了
Correct!
这题有跳跃加分 我不建议你那么做
There's a hopping bonus here,but I don't suggest you take it.
好吧
Okay.
这题是声音题 宝宝发出这种声音时你该怎么办？
This is an audio question. What do you do when a baby makes this sound:
检查她是尿湿或饿了，帮她拍背
Check if it's wet or hungry,burp it.
太棒了，你要再回答一题 或抽魔法机会牌？
Excellent! Now do you want another question or a Wicked Wango Card?
-我要抽牌 -对不起
-A card! A card! I pick a card! -Oh,I'm sorry.
你出局了 你会是个烂妈妈
You've been Bamboozled! You're gonna be a terrible mother!
我忘记我们为什么要这么做了
I've lost sight of why we're doing this!
请不要走开
Please don't walk away.
我说得太过火了
I've gone too far.